'use strict';
const LinkedList = require('../LinkedList');

// let test = new LinkedList();

let questions = [
  {
    'question': 'carro',
    'answer': 'car',
  },
  {
    'question': 'perro',
    'answer': 'dog',
  },
  {
    'question': 'casa',
    'answer': 'house',
  },
  {
    'question': 'autopista',
    'answer': 'highway',
  },
  {
    'question': 'biblioteca',
    'answer': 'library',
  },
  {
    'question': 'chaqueta',
    'answer': 'jacket',
  },
  {
    'question': 'pantalones',
    'answer': 'pants',
  },
  {
    'question': 'Sonrojado',
    'answer': 'blushing',
  },
  {
    'question': 'traducir',
    'answer': 'translate',
  },
  {
    'question': 'irrumpir',
    'answer': 'burst',
  }
];

// function main(){
//   let questions = new LinkedList();
//   allQuestions.forEach(item => {
//     questions.insertLast(item);
//   });
//   return questions;
// }

module.exports = questions;
// module.exports = main;